[Episode 20]
[Longevity]
Mother, be careful.
Everyone, please take your seats.
Take your seats.
Today is my mother's eightieth birthday.
Thank you all for coming.
I am deeply grateful.
Now, let's raise a cup together.
- Sure.
- A long, healthy, and happy life
to my mother.
Ms. Yan, the Zhao family is truly rich.
For starters,
they ordered premium bird's nest.
Their deposit alone
equals our entire month's revenue.
Thank you both for coming.
- Congratulations.
- Today is a fine day.
Cheers. A happy, long life
to you.
Cheers!
Making money is secondary.
If we pull off this birthday banquet,
Bofeng House's reputation will surely soar.
- Mother, it's me!
- Mother!
What's going on?
Go!
Murder!
What did you feed us, you evil woman?
Ms. Yan!
Zhao Cai, close the door at once!
Jin Bao, go fetch a physician.
Everyone else, restrain the raving diners,
but be careful not to get hurt.
Yes.
According to the coroner,
those four had internal injuries,
and their pupils dilated.
It's exactly the mental symptom
of taking the Eternity Pill.
What's worse,
the poison does not act suddenly.
It accumulates over time,
incessantly injuring a person's mind.
Ling Yun Fei is behind it.
These people can move upon hearing a whistle.
They're clearly trained men.
So, those commoners
who vanished from the capital outskirts
have all been taken by Ling Yun Fei?
Your speculation is probably right.
Now, finding Ling Yun Fei's poison workshop
is the key to unraveling all these mysteries.
Those four all died.
Liu Ru Yan was also silenced.
All our leads are dead.
Perhaps we can start
with the ingredient of Eternity Pill.
Yin Qing, what did you get?
Miss, I've examined it carefully.
The ingredient of Eternity Pill
is called Fuqing herb.
Its petals are purple and spread open.
Its stamens are pure white,
and its leaves are emerald green.
It grows in staggered fashion
along the stems.
But its growing environment
is particularly unique.
It favors only damp, warm places.
Mr. Yin, what a surprise.
You know quite a lot.
With so many skills,
how come you were not
given important jobs before?
It's not easy to meet someone
who can see my talent.
So I'm thankful to Miss Meng
for recognizing my talent.
Sure, you have talent.
Yin Qing,
if I did not know your abilities,
I would really suspect
that you got into the Censorate
through flattery alone.
The Fuqing herb has quite a strong nature.
In the short term, it causes hallucinations.
Long-term use of it leads to madness.
Users will even draw a sword
at the sight of a mosquito.
Then how does it differ from Wushi Powder?
Its potency is a thousand times stronger
than Wushi Powder, and it's highly addictive.
Apart from the mental euphoria,
users' physical strength surges wildly,
leading to exhaustion and death.
If this virulent poison spreads
among the common folk,
it will pose a deadly threat to the people.
This poison endangers the people's safety.
If we allow it to circulate,
the whole country will be in grave peril.
Nian, do you know of any unique valley
fit for the Fuqing herb's growth?
Although such a valley is rare,
our country is vast with various valleys.
And finding the right one is
like looking for a needle in a haystack.
Since you all haven't eaten yet,
I made some pastries.
You're talented, yet you rarely cook.
Are these edible?
You don't have to eat.
- Someone will--
- I love them.
Mr. Shen, usually, you sweet-talk us,
but why are you so picky
with your own sister?
I was wrong.
How dare I say
my own sister's cooking is not good?
Look, even the plating is
as beautiful as a carefully painted picture.
The painting!
Liu Ru Yan's painting!
Yin Qing.
Liu Ru Yan hid this painting
in a secret compartment,
which means the place depicted is not fake.
She might have actually been there.
Hibiscus flowers favor warm, humid places,
just like the Fuqing herb.
Di Nian, take men immediately
and search the outskirts for similar areas.
Miss Meng.
Something really bad
happened at Bofeng House!
Stop!
Give me back my husband!
- Stop!
- What's going on?
Fu Zhi!
Miss Meng, you must do justice!
I held the birthday banquet here
only for your sake.
If anything happens to my husband,
how can I possibly go on living?
Even with your backing, Miss Meng,
Ms. Yan must give us an explanation.
Right! Without an explanation,
none of you are leaving.
Nobody is leaving!
What are you doing?
Stop it!
Those who want justice,
save the people with me.
Those who want to cause trouble,
I will not let you off.
Save them!
My lord!
Miss Meng, the liquor is poisoned.
Judging from the intense medicinal property,
it is very likely Eternity Pill.
Huxiao Gang!
They did this to get back at me.
These people must be treated immediately,
or their lives are in danger.
Where is Miss Yan? She was just here.
- How did she disappear suddenly?
- Miss Meng.
Meng Ting Hui,
you killed the one I love most.
I will make your best friend suffer.
If you want to save Yan Fu Zhi, come alone.
Otherwise, you'll see her dead body.
Fu Zhi!
If the court does not hand over Meng Ting Hui
before the hour of Xu today,
I'll kill everyone in the entire capital
with the Eternity Pill.
By Ling Yun Fei.
Shun.
Run!
Absurd!
A mere Huxiao Gang is quite brazen!
Your Majesty.
The Huxiao Gang must be eradicated,
and Ling Yun Fei must be captured.
The people also need to be pacified.
I have heard
that many were poisoned at Bofeng House,
and local clinics are overwhelmed.
The city is also full of threatening letters,
causing widespread panic.
All this stems from Meng Ting Hui.
If we just hand her over,
we can appease both Ling Yun Fei
and the people.
That's the best way.
Your Majesty, I second that.
Although Meng Ting Hui punishes evildoers,
she has also provoked the Huxiao Gang.
Your Majesty, if you still shield her,
it may damage your image.
Ling Yun Fei posted threatening letters
all over the city.
Is he provoking Meng Ting Hui?
He is provoking me and the national prestige!
If I compromise,
that will truly damage my image.
Your Majesty,
all officials are now waiting outside.
If Your Majesty refuses to hand her over,
they may not agree.
Today, let alone Meng Ting Hui,
even if it were any other official,
I will never compromise.
Instead of thinking
how to fight the gang together,
both of you are here forcing me
to hand her over.
Your Majesty, there are less than six hours
before the hour of Xu.
If the search yields no results,
and Huxiao Gang kills the commoners
with the Eternity Pill,
how will we deal with it then?
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, Miss Meng has come to see you
and has volunteered
to go and meet Ling Yun Fei.
Seal all exits.
- Search.
- Yes!
Your Majesty, the situation is most urgent.
Please allow me to go alone.
This concerns national dignity.
It is not the time for you to play the hero.
I've already sent Zhi Shu,
Di Nian, and Huang Bo
to search the entire city
for the Huxiao Gang and Ling Yun Fei.
That's it.
Ling Yun Fei is convinced
that I killed Liu Ru Yan
and wants a life for a life.
If my life can be exchanged
for Fu Zhi and the people of the capital--
Meng Ting Hui!
This involves the dark forces.
Do you take this as child's play?
I won't change my mind.
You may leave.
I won't change my mind either.
Even if it means death, I must go.
Miss Meng actually defied His Majesty.
She is quite bold.
Miss Meng.
Zhi Shu has gone to search for Miss Yan.
His Majesty has also sent the Divine Guards
to search the capital.
They will surely find Fu Zhi.
Why must you risk your own life?
I am going for Fu Zhi,
and also for the people of the capital.
Ling Yun Fei wants me.
It is time to settle things with him.
Miss Meng, we knew we couldn't dissuade you.
How about letting me go instead?
Having worked with you for so long,
I can imitate your words and actions.
Ling Yun Fei won't recognize the difference.
Can Ling Yun Fei not tell a man from a woman?
Ling Yun Fei asked me to come alone.
If he sees anyone else,
Fu Zhi's life will be in danger.
This game must be played by his rules.
Miss Meng, if you insist on going,
drink this soup.
It's made with Qi Supplement.
You may have no internal strength,
but it can help you become strong and agile.
You must drink it, or we cannot let you go.
Exactly.
At least taking this
will reassure us a little.
I'm leaving.
You drugged me!
Forgive us, Miss Meng.
We had no better choice.
She can sleep
until the hour of Chen tomorrow.
When she wakes up,
whether she punishes me or hates me,
I will take it.
I will immediately take men to find Miss Yan.
I will also re-check the clues
from Wanxiang Pavilion.
Search carefully, all of you!
Yes.
Found it.
Your Majesty.
This is the fluorite powder left
by Miss Meng.
If you are determined to go,
I will send men to protect you secretly.
Ling Yun Fei wants me to go alone.
If he senses anything else, Fu Zhi's life--
This is my final concession.
You are a subject of mine.
I'll never put you in danger.
Leave markings along the way.
Zhi Shu and Di Nian will follow covertly.
Ling Yun Fei will absolutely not detect them.
When I meet Ling Yun Fei,
I will release a crimson flame as the signal.
Remember,
keeping you and Miss Yan safe
is the top priority.
It's dark, and the forest is deep.
There may be an ambush, Your Majesty.
Perhaps you should return.
We will surely rescue Miss Meng and Miss Yan.
Huang is right.
Ling Yun Fei is cruel. If he harms--
That's why I must capture them personally.
[Censorate]
Let's go to the imperial palace.
Le Yan!
Sir, why are you here so late?
Ling Yun Fei is cunning and peculiar.
And the Censorate is his first target.
So I'm worried about you.
Are you going home?
I'm going to the imperial palace.
Le Yan,
what is so urgent?
Miss Meng is missing.
She must have gone
to meet Ling Yun Fei alone.
Yin Qing has taken the Light Cavalry
out of the city.
But if there is no one to back her up,
she will be in danger going alone.
I must report to His Majesty
and ask him to send reinforcements.
Where are Captain Di and Zhi Shu right now?
Zhi Shu went long ago
to search for Miss Yan and Ling Yun Fei.
Nian is probably with His Majesty.
Ling Yun Fei will surely
get back at the entire Censorate.
Since Zhi Shu and Di Nian are away,
who will protect your family?
You mobilize guards immediately
to defend your family.
I will go to see His Majesty in your stead.
But if His Majesty asks about the details--
His Majesty knows Miss Meng very well.
I will report properly to His Majesty.
Don't worry.
Take care of yourself and your family.
Miss Meng.
Haven't you always wanted to catch me?
No more talking.
I am already here.
Release Yan Fu Zhi right now.
Be patient.
The real show is just beginning.
Let me go!
Fu Zhi!
I've often dreamed of you recently.
In my dreams, you were just like this,
kneeling at my feet begging for mercy.
I truly cannot understand.
You and I were not enemies
in the first place.
Why do you always target me relentlessly?
You destroyed all the foundations I built.
And you killed the woman I love most.
So,
how should I deal with you?
Ling Yun Fei,
you can do whatever you want
with me.
But right now, release Yan Fu Zhi first.
If you hurt her,
I will crush you to dust.
What good sisters. So touching.
You've been investigating the Eternity Pill,
haven't you?
Meng!
Let her go!
Let her go and come at me!
I'll grant your wish.
Ling Yun Fei!
Don't you touch Fu Zhi!
The real killer of Liu Ru Yan
is someone else.
You've got the wrong enemy.
Even if we both die today,
Liu Ru Yan will not rest in peace.
I came here alone today.
I'm not even afraid of death,
so why would I lie?
That day, I needed
to find your whereabouts from Liu Ru Yan,
so how could I rashly kill her?
Even if she didn't kill Ru Yan personally,
she caused Ru Yan's death,
my brother's death,
and the deaths of dozens of brothers.
If we don't cut her to pieces today,
we'll fail Ru Yan and other dead brothers.
Yes, this is the place.
We're pressed for time.
Come on.
Sir!
Ying Gua has led troops into the Huxiao Gang.
It's inadvisable to confront them.
Stop it! Let her go!
Fu Zhi!
Get off of her!
Didn't you want revenge? Come at me!
Stop!
Stop it!
Get off of her!
No! Stop!
Don't!
You're her best friend.
So you eat these for her.
Listen, I killed Liu Ru Yan.
I killed her.
I did it.
I watched her die by my hand.
Before she died, she put on the best makeup
and wore her fanciest clothes.
She was looking forward to seeing you.
What a pity.
You didn't even get to see her one last time.
You want to avenge her death, right?
Kill me!
Kill me right now!
I'll now kill you to avenge Ru Yan's death!
Ling Yun Fei!
Fu Zhi!
Master!
Raid the Huxiao Gang!
- Chase them!
- Yes!
Fu Zhi!
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Fu Zhi, what's wrong with you?
She was fed Eternity Pills.
Fu Zhi.
As you instructed,
Master Ling has evacuated safely.
Ling Yun Fei is a handy weapon.
Losing him would be a loss.
Besides, he knows too many secrets.
Dead or alive,
he must not fall into the court's hands.
No worries, Master.
The court has raided the Huxiao Gang,
but the secret passage has been destroyed.
They won't find him in a short time.
Fu Zhi!
Calm down!
Stop breaking things! Fu Zhi!
Fu Zhi, calm down!
Hold on!
Fu Zhi, stop breaking things!
Stop it!
Fu Zhi!
Hold on!
Just get through it, and you'll be fine.
Hold on a little longer, alright?
It's alright.
Meng.
Quick, give me the Eternity Pill.
Please. Give me the Eternity Pill.
I feel so awful, so awful.
- Fu Zhi!
- Give me the Eternity Pill!
Just get over it, and you'll be fine.
Zhi Shu, give me the Eternity Pill.
Please, give me the Eternity Pill.
I feel so awful.
Give me the Eternity Pill, please!
Fu Zhi, that will destroy you.
I feel so awful.
Fu Zhi!
Wake up!
Fu Zhi, let go!
- Stop biting!
- Miss Meng!
- Fu Zhi!
We have to tie up Miss Yan.
When her symptoms flare, she will hurt us.
Let go!
Give me the Eternity Pill!
Or I will kill you all!
Yan Fu Zhi, put down the knife!
Fu Zhi, don't hurt yourself!
Miss Yan!
Mr. Shen, give me a hand!
Let me go!
Miss Meng, if we don't tie her up,
she will hurt herself too.
Fu Zhi.
Kill me, please!
I'm in so much pain.
It's too painful.
Please.
Kill me. Just kill me!
Kill me!
Fu Zhi!
Yin Qing,
you're skilled in toxicology.
Please. Please save Fu Zhi.
- Miss Meng!
- Please, think of a way.
Get up.
I'm begging you. Think of a way, please!
Fu Zhi is my only family.
I can exchange my life
for her life.
Miss Meng, get up.
To save Miss Yan,
I promise I will
give everything I have.
Miss Meng, Mr. Shen,
this poison is rather strange.
The imperial physician sent by His Majesty
can't treat her either.
I've searched through all medical books
and found no cure.
Also, it could take months
and even years to develop an antidote.
But Miss Yan...
I'm afraid she can last only three days.
If she can get through it on her own,
the toxicity will naturally weaken.
Three days?
Three days!
Fu Zhi.
Hold on!
Bofeng House hasn't expanded
across the country.
Forget high official positions or wealth.
I don't want any of it.
Let's go back to Shazhou.
I just want you to be safe and sound.
Please.
Don't leave me behind.
I'm begging you.
I heard
Jiang Mei Er came picking on you again.
She really thinks we're easy to bully!
Look, I'll smash her
with my abacus right now.
But in my opinion,
nothing is worth risking your life.
Let's go make our fortune in the capital.
You open a restaurant,
and I'll pursue an official career.
We will surely make it
- in the capital.
- Capital, here we come!
This is the luckiest draw I got for you
at Lingquan Temple.
The master who interpreted the lot said
you will definitely pass the exam.
I hope I can become an official
and change my destiny.
I hope I can protect the ones closest to me.
I've already worked so hard.
I've worked very hard.
Meng.
I know you have.
I've seen your hard work.
Even if you don't pass the exams,
you're still the best in the world.
You are the one and only Meng Ting Hui.
Fu Zhi, I'm the Zhuangyuan!
I'm the Zhuangyuan!
Meng, here I am.
You're talented.
You'll get what you want!
You're so cruel.
We promised to go back to Shazhou together.
You broke your promise.
You must promise me.
When helping others, protect yourself first.
Stop!
Stop it!
Get off of her!
Please, give me the Eternity Pill.
I'll do what you say.
What if I ask you to kill Meng Ting Hui?
Okay, I'll kill her.
I'll kill her.
Fu Zhi.
Wake up.
Ms. Yan, this is Miss Meng!
Let go of her.
Miss Meng, are you alright?
I am here.
Meng, it's killing me.
It's like bugs are biting all over my body.
Please, kill me.
There are bugs.
Bugs are biting me.
They're gnawing at my bones. It's killing me.
Yin Qing, get her up.
Be careful!
Fu Zhi, be careful.
Meng.
Kill me, please.
Please.
- Please.
- If you die,
what will I do?
If you die,
I won't live either.
I have the Eternity Pill here.
Give it to me! Right now!
Fu Zhi!
Give it to me!
Shen Zhi Shu,
do you want to make her die faster?
Do you want to watch her die in agony?
Meng Ting Hui, you're her best friend.
Don't you want her to die
a little more comfortably?
She won't die.
She absolutely will not die!
If she...
If she really...
I'll die with her.
I will never let her be alone.
I just...
I just can't see her in such pain.
Miss Meng.
Our caravans often travel to the border
and search for the Ice Soul Pill.
- It counters the heat of Wushi Powder.
- Fu Zhi.
It's not an antidote for the Eternity Pill,
but it's much similar.
In a life-or-death situation,
I hope this will help Miss Yan get over it.
Miss Meng, it's not a perfect remedy,
but it is worth a try.
Fu Zhi.
If this medicine kills you,
I will die with you.
- Fu Zhi.
- Let me check.
Fu Zhi.
Her pulse is weak, but the rate is stable.
Tonight, at the hour of Zi,
if the heat poison doesn't surge again,
she will be out of danger.
We owe much to you, Miss Situ.
Miss Yan and Miss Meng treated me
like a sister,
so it's the least I can do.
Tonight, Miss Yan is in critical condition.
I will leave now and not disturb you all.
It's late. I will see you out.
[Censorate]
Zhi Li, why are you still here so late?
Why are you crying?
Who made you cry?
I originally thought
that Miss Meng was afraid of nothing.
But when Miss Yan's addiction flared up,
Miss Meng hysterically cried,
and even Zhi Shu cried.
Nian, I am so scared.
I'm afraid Miss Yan will never wake up again.
I'm even more afraid
something might happen to you.
Zhi Li, I've returned safely.
I am fine.
You've really grown bolder.
Before sunset, Mr. Huang already
took the Light Cavalry and Divine Guards back.
Yet you actually acted alone
and didn't return all night.
What if you had encountered danger?
Zhi Li, does your hand hurt?
I've returned safely, haven't I?
Can't you let me worry less?
You just called me Zhi Li.
Do you think you've grown up
and don't have to listen to me?
Call me sister.
Sister.
Stop pretending to be pitiful.
Are you injured?
I've never seen Zhi Shu look so worried.
In truth, he has long been into Miss Yan,
but he has always dissembled
and refused to admit it.
Now, since Miss Yan is suffering,
he is naturally heartbroken.
I hope Miss Yan can pull through tonight.
If anything happens to her,
the light in his eyes
may be extinguished forever.
And Miss Meng will collapse.
I'll surely bring Ling Yun Fei to justice.
I hope Miss Yan will get through it.
How did you get so badly injured?
I accidentally scraped myself
while searching the valleys on the outskirts.
It was a long way away,
so I returned a bit late.
Did you find anything there?
It still needs more time.
You were gone
for a whole day and night without news
and came back with wounds.
Do you have any idea how worried I was?
Why are you smiling?
You care about me.
When have I not cared about you?
You'd better go see a physician tomorrow.
Got it.
What is this?
I found this while searching the valleys.
I heard that carrying it brings good luck.
I think you are the one
who needs some good luck.
You take a rest. I'll go check on Miss Yan.
I'll go with you.
You rest well and return home early.
[Bofeng House]
Madam.
I wonder how Ms. Yan is doing.
You usually compete fiercely
for business with Ms. Yan,
but you still care about her quite a bit.
These are two different things.
Haven't you seen
how terrifying those Eternity Pill users are?
The head of the Zhao family and his mother
are both dead.
It's not easy for a woman like Ms. Yan
to build her career out there.
Thanks to Miss Meng, she was saved.